This is... Demon Snuff?
這是…魔香
He is not fully demonised yet.
魔物化不完全
He can still turn back to his human form.
他還能變回人類
Someone's coming! Run!
有人過來了 快逃
You let a demon go.
你…放走魔物了
What are you talking about?
學長在說什麼
You are really a girl.
果然是女的
Who are you?
妳是誰
I'M A VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER, SO I'M GOING TO KEEP THE LAST BOSS!
《因為是反派大小姐》 《所以養了魔王》
THE VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER DOESN'T ALLOW EVIL DEEDS
(反派大小姐不允許惡事)
The church's investigative ability is nothing much.
教會的調查能力也不怎麼樣嘛
I know who you and Senior Kyle are.
我可是知道你和凱魯學長是什麼人
What?
什麼
Mirchetta's cleaners,
米爾契塔的肅清者
"Nameless Priests".
"無名祭司"
You are raised secretly by the church
教會為了討伐魔物 暗中培育的
while strengthening with Demon Snuff.
藉由魔香而強化的人類
You infiltrated the academy with the church's help to hunt demons.
為了找到正在追查的魔物 教會讓你們混入學園
Perhaps there's a possibility that someone is using Demon Snuff here.
因為或許在學園內能使用魔香
I'm going to ask you again.
我再問一次
Who are you?
妳是什麼人
Don't worry.
放心吧
I won't tell anyone your identities.
我不會跟任何人說出你們的身份
In return, can you help me keep a secret as well?
相對的 能否也能幫我保密
Fine.
好吧
I doubt I'll benefit from exposing the fact that you are a girl.
公開妳是女性的事 對我也沒什麼好處
I'm glad that we've reached an agreement.
很高興我們達成共識
What are we going to do with the teacher?
那麼 該怎麼處理教授
I'll think of something later.
之後我會想辦法
Anyway, his witness testimony...
反正他的目擊證詞…
It'll probably be something vague.
也會被含糊過去吧
Senior, do you want to investigate this thoroughly?
學長 要不要認真調查一下
Perhaps you might find something. Demon Snuff, for example.
搞不好會出現什麼關鍵 比方說魔香
Forget it. They probably did it on purpose.
算了吧 八成是那些傢伙故意的
Let's go back.
回去吧
Aili.
小艾
Seems like Aili is a part of your real name.
看來妳的本名裡有個"艾"字啊
I'm not going to tell you that.
不告訴你
That's cold of you.
真冷淡
We do share each other's secrets after all.
我們可是知道彼此秘密的同伴呢
I was just trying to help my friend who was beaten up by my fiance.
我只是想幫忙被未婚夫毆打的朋友
Is your friend a victim of the vampire incident?
妳的朋友 是吸血鬼事件的被害者嗎
Be clear about it.
說清楚啊
Rachel.
蕾切爾
Can you tell us slowly?
能慢慢說給我們聽嗎
My friend's fiance is addicted to a strange kind of incense.
我朋友的未婚夫 迷上一種奇怪的調香
I told Selena as well.
我也曾跟塞蕾娜說過
Incense? Does she mean Demon Snuff?
調香 指的是魔香嗎
When I was in a dilemma, Professor Koenig came to help me.
正當我在煩惱時 凱尼教授找上我
He said he wanted to teach me and my friend how to terminate the engagement.
說要教我和我朋友 如何解除婚約
That was why you introduced your friend to the professor, right?
所以妳才介紹朋友跟教授見面
I didn't expect something like that to happen.
沒想到 會發生那件事
Later, the professor asked you to go out, right?
之後 教授就找妳出來是嗎
Yes.
是
Although I'm afraid of him blackmailing me,
雖然我很怕教授勒索我
I still hope for things to improve.
但還是希望事情能有所進展…
Seems like you had been the professor's target since the beginning.
看來 妳一開始 就成為教授的目標了
The professor wouldn't have come to you if he was targeting the victim.
如果教授把受害者當目標 就不會找上妳了
Is that so?
原來是這樣啊…
No matter what, the professor has to pay for what he did.
不管怎麼說 必須讓教授償還罪行
He likes gambling.
教授喜歡賭博
Apparently, he's saddled himself with monstrous debt.
據說現在輸了一屁股債
He's also addicted to a type of weird incense.
好像也迷上奇怪的調香
That makes things easy.
那就好辦了
Ruining the professor while keeping the whole incident a secret.
不讓事件曝光 又能毀了教授
I don't want to be his enemy indeed.
我果然還是不想與他為敵
It's done.
解決了
It's so scary to have such an excellent subordinate.
部下優秀過頭好可怕
How did you do it?
你怎麼解決的
I invited him to a poker game
我邀教授玩撲克牌賭錢
and got him to talk about Rachel.
然後套出蕾切爾的事
Then, I made him lose.
讓他輸個精光
I remember he is very good at poker.
我記得 教授很會玩撲克牌
I'm good at cheating.
我很擅長出老千
A debt letter?
借據
The sum on this...
上面的金額…
With this in our hands, he'll have to listen to anything we say.
只要有這個 要殺要剮隨便我們
What about Demon Snuff? Did he say anything about that?
魔香呢 他有說什麼嗎
I think he used a pipe he picked up coincidentally.
聽說是用偶然撿到的調香
He didn't know much about it.
也不清楚詳細狀況
What a useless professor.
真沒用的教授
Next, we need to make this incident into an accident.
再來就是把這次的事件 操弄成一場意外
Prove the victim's innocence
證明被害者的清白
and terminate Rachel's engagement with his fiance.
還有讓蕾切爾 跟未婚夫解除婚約是嗎
There are many things to be considered.
得考慮許多事情
Let's start now.
那就現在開始吧
All right, Rachel?
好嗎 蕾切爾
Anyway, I'll get the professor's matter settled.
總之 我去收尾教授的事
Are you not sure whether to trust him or not?
不知道該不該相信他嗎
That's not it.
不是這樣的…
You only trusted the wrong person.
妳只是相信錯對象了
Remember this.
請銘記在心
A man might have hurt you
傷害妳的或許是男性
but a man also helped you.
但幫助妳的人也是男性
I want to become a special existence.
我想成為特別的存在
A cool girl who helps other girls like Selena.
想像塞蕾娜小姐那樣 成為幫助女性的帥氣女生
I will terminate the engagement myself.
我會自己解除婚約
I won't be able to change anything if I keep acting weak.
再這樣懦弱下去 什麼也無法改變
That's great.
這樣就好
I don't want to live while being fearful of others' moods.
我不想再過著看人臉色的生活
So, can you let me join the guard unit?
所以 能否讓我加入警衛隊
Of course.
當然沒問題
I look forward to working with you, Rachel.
請多指教了 蕾切爾
Yes, Master Aili.
好的 艾里大人
Nice working with you.
請多指教
Are you going to join as well?
學長也要加入嗎…
We know each other's secret, right?
我們是知道彼此秘密的同伴吧
Let's get working then.
那就開始工作吧
Get President James' approval to use this empty classroom as the guard unit's office.
請跟賽姆斯會長申請許可 把這間空教室當作警衛隊辦公室
That's easy.
小事一樁
I'll clean the office.
我來打掃辦公室
I'm going to borrow some cleaning tools.
我去借打掃用具
How do we report the vampire incident to President James?
吸血鬼騷動事件 如何跟賽姆斯會長報告
Report the truth.
如實報告
I'll put in a remark to not make it public for the students' benefit.
但我會註明為了不影響學生 最好不要公開
That's surprising.
真意外
I thought the young lady full of justice
我以為充滿正義的大小姐
will try to expose every evil deed to the public.
會把一切惡行攤在陽光下呢
An underling is nothing important.
那種小嘍囉根本就不重要
Besides, the true culprit is someone else.
而且 真正的犯人另有其人
I'm going to find James then.
那我去找賽姆斯了
All right!
好耶
Darn it! That was the last one!
可惡 那是最後一個
A victory in the battle!
搶購爭奪戰獲勝
It's such a relief to be in the Otome game with Pork Cutlet Sandwich.
在有豬排三明治的 乙女遊戲世界裡真是太好了
Look at this.
快看這個
To Master Auguste.
給奧古斯特大人
Who wrote this?
是誰寫的
-You appeared in my dreams. -That letter...
-你出現在我的夢裡 -那封信…
I'm from the guard unit! Get away from the notice board immediately!
我是警衛隊 全部離開公告欄
What?
幹嘛
We are just looking at something posted on the board. Is there a problem?
我們只是在看被貼出來的東西 有什麼問題嗎
You are quite arrogant.
會不會太囂張了
It's one against three. This is difficult.
一對三 可能有點困難
Why are you making a fuss?
你們在吵什麼
Senior Kyle.
凱魯學長
It's ungentlemanly to outnumber someone in an argument.
多數欺負少數 不是君子的行為
-Let's go. -Sure. Darn it.
-走吧 -好 可惡
Senior Kyle. Thank you.
凱魯學長 謝謝你
You are so gentle.
你真溫柔
Gentle? Don't be mistaken.
溫柔 你可別搞錯了
A gentle person won't do this.
溫柔的人不會做這種事
I think ripping up the letter is the right thing to do though.
可是我覺得撕掉信是正確的做法
What?
什麼
This is definitely the Kyle route.
我記得 這是凱魯路線
"SELENA, THIS IS AN IMPORTANT LETTER" Selena even return
(塞蕾娜 這是重要的信) 遊戲中的塞蕾娜
"I COLLECTED THE PIECES AND RESTORED IT" the letter to her friend
(我收集起來恢復原狀了) 還特地把信還給朋友
"PLEASE TAKE IT" in the game.
(收下吧)
It's cruel to return it to the sender.
直接退回比較殘忍
You are a weird one.
奇怪的傢伙
Why are you following me? I don't want anything to do with you.
幹嘛跟著我 別跟我扯上關係
I also want to see the cats behind the academy.
因為 我也想看校園後方的貓咪
I can see the cat food sticking out of your pocket.
我看到你的口袋裡 裝著貓咪零食
That's...
這是…
Found you. Aili...
找到了 小艾…
What? Kyle is here as well?
什麼嘛 凱魯也在
What happened?
發生什麼事了
Ashtart has released a statement.
阿斯塔蒂 放出聲明了
What is the content?
內容是什麼
"To the human fools who are not willing to hand over the Holy Sword Maiden's head."
"不願交出聖劍少女首級的" "愚蠢人類們"
"Misha Academy is next."
"接下來就是迷夏學園"
"I'll make it rain blood during the school festival. Regret your actions."
"我將在學園祭降下血雨" "好好懺悔吧"
What will the academy do in response?
學園方面將如何應對
The principal is still sick.
學園長還臥病在床
The one who replaces him...
代替他的是…
The principal's proxy will come to make regular visits.
代理大公會定期來巡視
The principal's proxy is...
代理大公是…
Master Claude?
庫洛德大人
WALT LIZANIS CV TOSHIYUKI TOYONAGA
(沃魯特 利札尼絲) (CV 豐永利行)
A CHARACTER THAT CAN BE KEPT IN "REGALIA OF SAINTS, DEMONS AND MAIDENS 2".
(聖與魔與少女的雷加利亞2裡的) (可攻略角色之一)
A HANDSOME CHARACTER WHO IS GOOD AT SOCIALISING. THE ACCOUNTANT OF THE STUDENT COUNCIL.
(是位帥氣又善於交際的角色) (在學生會擔任會計一職)
POPULAR AND GENTLE TO GIRLS. HOWEVER, THIS IS JUST A FACADE.
(對女學生溫柔 也很受歡迎) (但這只是他的表面)
HE IS ACTUALLY A PERSON WITH SECRETS.
(其實他是有秘密的人)
The school festival is an important event at Misha Academy.
學園祭是迷夏學園的重要活動
There are two major events.
其中有兩項活動
On the first day, there's the swordsmanship contest.
第一天是劍術大賽
In the video game, there's an event where the church that organised the games
在遊戲中 主辦大賽的教會
mixes Demon Snuff in the prizes
在獎品中混入了魔香
and turns James into a demon.
讓賽姆斯變成魔物的事件
By overcoming this event,
只要撐過這個魔物化事件
the duchy of Mirchetta will avoid destruction
就能避免米爾契塔公國的滅亡
and the Bad End can be avoided.
也能避免BE發生
Another major event
另一個大型活動
is the ball on the second day where "Princess Lily White" will be chosen.
就是第二天選出 "白百合公主"的舞會
It's a pageant contest, in short.
簡單來說就是選美小姐
The students are already looking for a suitable partner for the ball.
學生們已經在尋找舞會的搭檔了
You won't dance with me?
妳不跟我跳舞
How can you be so arrogant when you are just a commoner?
明明是平民還敢這麼囂張
But...
可…可是
Well, just calm down.
好了 冷靜點
Both of you are quite suitable for each other.
兩位其實很登對啊
You have yet to decide who you want to dance with, right?
妳還沒決定要跟誰跳舞吧
But I have someone I would like to invite.
可是 我有想邀約的人
Auguste will be busy during the school festival so he might not participate in the ball.
奧古斯特在學園祭當天會很忙 可能不參加舞會
Seriously.
討厭
She wanted to invite Master Auguste?
她居然想邀奧古斯特大人
She's aiming too high.
太高攀了吧
I invited you because you are ugly and pitiful...
看妳這種醜八怪可憐 所以我才邀妳跳…
That's the wrong way to ask a lady. Try again.
邀約女性的方式不對 重來
A duck? Who are you?
鴨子為什麼…你是誰
I'm just a nameless ordinary duck.
誰都不是 我只是個無名的普通鴨子
This voice... It's Aili Kahlua, right?
這個聲音 是艾里 加爾吧
Keep your nonsense in check.
胡鬧也有個限度吧
I only kicked a guy away who ran his mouth while looking for a partner.
我只是把尋找舞伴時 口出問題發言的男生踢走而已
I think doing that is better than posting a friend's letter on the notice board.
我覺得這個行為 比把朋友的信貼在公告欄好多了
What are you saying?
你在說什麼
I saw you accepting the girl's letter.
我可是看到妳收下了 那女孩寫的信喔
Are you trying to say that I did that? I don't think anyone will believe you.
你想說是我做的嗎 應該沒人相信喔
It's all right. I'm only confirming the facts.
沒關係 我只是確認事實而已
Demon King!
魔王
Master Claude.
庫洛德大人
What a big academy As expected of a prestigious school.
好大的校園 不愧是名門學校
I was worried about their reaction when they see the Demon King.
我本來還擔心大家看到魔王 會有什麼反應
Demon King. The meeting will start soon. We are short on time.
魔王 會議差不多要開始了 沒時間了
Belzebuth can read the time now!
佩魯賽博特 會看錶了
No. I want to see the academy.
不 我想確認校園
Ashtart's attack has to be avoided.
必須避免阿斯塔蒂的襲擊
He won't attack the place. No demon can win against the Demon King.
他不可能來襲擊 因為沒有魔物贏得了魔王
Bel, set your biases aside.
佩魯 丟掉你的先入為主觀念
You can do it.
你做的到
Master Claude is teaching him.
庫洛德大人在教他
He was so overprotective at first.
他原本是這麼地寵他
Speaking of which, I have something to confirm.
對了 我想確認一件事
Is there a duck student in this academy?
這所學園裡 有鴨子學生嗎
A duck?
鴨子
President James!
賽姆斯會長
Have you taken your break yet? Let me show the principal around instead.
你還沒休息吧 換我帶學園長參觀校園
-Are you sure? -Yes.
-可以嗎 -可以
If the principal hasn't had lunch yet,
如果學園長也還沒吃午餐的話
let me take you to the dining hall.
我帶您到食堂去吧
I remember that Selena idolised the Holy Sword Maiden.
我記得塞蕾娜 應該很憧憬聖劍少女吧
He is the Demon King! Are you sure it's all right?
他可是魔王耶 這樣好嗎
Keith and Bel, both of you may return.
吉斯和佩魯先回去
I'll go and patrol the academy with her.
我跟她稍微巡視一下校園
Well, that's fine.
是可以啦
Thanks for your help.
拜託你們了
Well, you are...
那麼 妳是…
Please call me Selena.
請稱呼我塞蕾娜吧
Selena, please lead the way.
塞蕾娜 帶我參觀吧
Sure. Leave it to me.
好的 交給我吧
Well...
那…
Can I call you Master Claude?
我能稱呼您庫洛德大人嗎
Sure but please refrain from being intimate.
可以 但請別叫得太親密
My fiancee is very jealous.
我的未婚妻 嫉妒心很強的
His face is really a weapon.
他的表情果然是凶器
I want to cover it in a paper bag.
好想給他戴上紙袋
Due to Ashtart's statement,
因阿斯塔蒂的聲明
the principal has the intention to send some guards over.
學園長似乎要派騎士團過來
Who should we send to liaise...
我們要派誰去協調…
I'll go.
我 我去吧
No. It should be me.
不 應該是我
It's too dangerous for a girl.
對女生來說太危險了
Master Claude will protect me so it'll be fine.
庫洛德大人會保護我 所以沒關係
He is the Demon King though.
他可是魔王喔
The enemy of the Holy Sword Maiden you idolised.
是妳憧憬的聖劍少女的敵人
Enough! He's still human.
別說了 他還是人類
You are right.
是沒錯啦
Besides, the Holy Sword Maiden probably wants to save the Demon King too.
而且 既然是聖劍少女 應該也願意拯救魔王
So, I want to be the person to support him.
所以我想成為支持他的人
This girl...
這傢伙…
It's still too dangerous for a girl even if it's just as a liaison.
雖然只是協調 但派女生去太危險了
What if you offend the daughter of the Dautriche family?
萬一惹多德勒公爵家千金 不開心了怎麼辦
Exactly. She is the principal's fiancee...
就是說啊 她可是學園長的未婚…
That's exactly what I want.
如我所願
Apparently, she has an unforgiving personality.
聽說 公爵千金很有個性
She might come rushing here.
她搞不好會衝過來喔
The rumours say she is a young lady who has no knowledge at all.
傳聞她是個沒常識的千金大小姐
Since the Demon King didn't bring her here,
既然魔王都沒帶她過來
she might really be a problematic one.
搞不好真的很有問題
You'll all regret this moment in the future.
之後你們全部都給我記住
Oh. I think we've received a portrait of her.
對了 之前好像收到她的畫像
A portrait?
畫像
Yes. This is it.
對 就是這個
To be honest, I can't accept it.
老實說 我無法
I'm impressed at the Demon King's taste
我對於魔王的喜好佩服得五體投地
but I don't look forward to learning from him.
但我不想向他學習
I think he has strange taste because he is the Demon King.
我覺得應該是因為他是魔物 所以喜好比較特殊吧
I don't know who spread this portrait around but this person probably has a death wish.
不知道是誰散佈的 但這個人應該很想死吧
Their engagement must have been decided by the Dautriche family.
他們之間的婚約 一定是多德勒公爵家決定的
That is why I want to invite Master Claude to the school festival.
所以我打算邀請庫洛德大人 參加學園祭
I want to be chosen as Princess White Lily and be invited as Master Claude's partner.
我要被選上白百合公主 然後邀請庫洛德大人當舞伴…
It's almost time for me to live. After all, I need to go on patrol.
我差不多要走了 畢竟我還要巡邏
I'll go with you today.
今天我也跟你一起去吧
Me too.
我也是
I'll go as well then.
那我也一起
Why are all of you following me?
為什麼大家跟著我一起出來
Because that topic is a bit...
因為我對那方面的話題…
I'm not good with that as well.
我也不擅應對
Who's going to be the liaison?
那誰要做協調的工作
We'll just have to let her do it.
只能讓她去做吧
After all, the Demon King chose Selena.
畢竟魔王也指名塞蕾娜了
Is that so?
是喔
Master Claude chose her?
庫洛德大人指名
What's going on? Is he having an affair?
這是怎麼回事 他出軌了嗎
I think it's our first time walking together like this.
我們好像是第一次走在一起耶
I think so.
好像是吧
Guys like to gather and chat sometimes.
男生偶爾也想聚在一起聊聊嘛
It'll be better for the student council if we show a bit of unity.
大家稍微團結點 學生會就會變得更好
As expected of Aili. You just know what to say.
不愧是艾里 說得真好
Let's improve our relationship from now on.
大家以後要增進感情喔
I refuse.
我拒絕
It's good enough to carry out our own tasks.
各自做好分內工作就好
I don't like people getting in my way.
我不想喜歡被扯後腿
Why is everyone so cold?
幹嘛這麼冷淡
It's really hard for them to improve their relationship.
他們的確很難增進感情
After all, Walt and Kyle are assassins sent here to assassinate James.
畢竟沃魯特和凱魯 是被派來暗殺賽姆斯的刺客
Auguste is the character who defeats James in the end.
奧古斯特是最後打倒賽姆斯的角色
If it goes according to the game,
若按照遊戲進行
these four people are rivals who try to kill each other.
這四人是互相殘殺的對手
They must never learn James' true identity.
絕不能讓他們知道賽姆斯的真面目
There's a sweet smell.
有股甜膩的味道
James!
賽姆斯
Let me be...
別管我…
Oh no!
糟糕
Auguste, take President James to rest in the dorm!
奧古斯特 快帶賽姆斯會長 回宿舍休息
Sure! James, let's go.
好 賽姆斯 走吧
It's all right. I can walk... On my own.
沒關係 我能自己…走…
Stop saying nonsense. Your face is pale.
別說傻話了 你都臉色發青了
Aili Kahlua, report this to the teacher.
艾里 加爾 你去跟老師報告狀況
Me? But...
我嗎 可是…
Kyle, it's fine.
凱魯 沒關係
What?
什麼
Aili knows our true identity.
艾里知道我們的真面目
He might be from another organisation but he is one of our own.
雖是別的組織 但是我們的同伴
What?
什麼
But he is so weak.
可是他這麼纖弱…
That's because Aili is...
因為小艾是…
Hurry up and look for Demon Snuff.
快點去找魔香
It'll be troublesome if the demons are here.
魔物來了就麻煩了
Found it!
找到了
This is it, right?
就是這個吧
It's empty. It has a faint smell.
這是空的 味道也很淡
It doesn't feel like it is used to attract demons.
不像是引來魔物用的
Who put it here and for what reason then?
那到底是誰為了什麼放在這的
It's not the church that spreads the Demon Snuff, right?
不會是教會散播的魔香吧
The church spreads it and wants us to retrieve it? That's impossible.
教會灑魔香 然後要我們回收 怎麼可能
However, I have news that the church is planning to mix Demon Snuff
不過 我這裡收到教會打算 把魔香混入劍術大賽的獎品中
into the swordsmanship contest prizes to lure out the demons.
引出學園內魔物的情報
Stop joking!
開什麼玩笑
The church won't do something like that!
教會才不會做這種事
It's possible if they were paid though.
如果有錢的話的確有可能啦…
Those old sly priest foxes.
那些老狐狸祭司們
Walt!
沃魯特
Our mission's client is the Mirchetta family.
我們任務的委託人 是米爾契塔家族喔
The mission content also stems from their own family problems.
而且任務內容好像還是 他們自家的內訌問題
You actually revealed the secret of our mission in front of Aili?
你…居然在艾里面前 說出任務機密
Aili knows everything after all.
反正小艾都知道吧
I guess.
算是吧
From the game.
從遊戲中得知的
What is Demon Snuff?
魔香是什麼
Sorry. James say he was fine so...
抱歉 賽姆斯說沒事了 所以…
Aili and the both of you are from a secret organisation sent by the Elmir Empire?
艾里你們 是艾路梅亞王國 派遣過來的秘密組織
Incredible!
好強喔
That's right. Senior Walt and Senior Kyle are just apprentices.
沒錯 沃魯特學長和凱魯學長 還只是實習生
Aili... Are you our superior?
小艾…是我們的…上司…
Right?
對吧
-Yes. -That's right.
-對 -對…
You have more subordinates now.
僕人又增加了
The Demon Snuff you speak of. Does it make people violent?
你說的魔香 會讓人變兇暴是嗎
Yes.
對
Is that why there have been more incidents where female students are being bullied?
最近學園女學生被欺負的情況增加 也是這個原因吧
Now that he mentions it, I think so. I thought it was just a norm here.
經他這麼一說好像是 我以為這種情形是常態
We can't turn a blind eye since Demon Snuff appears in the academy.
既然魔香出現在學園內 那就不能放置不管
I will help too.
我也來幫忙
Thanks for your help.
你幫了大忙
James. You will help as well, right?
賽姆斯 你也會幫忙吧
Help these people who still seem to have something to hide?
幫這些 似乎還有事隱瞞的傢伙嗎
Demon stuff is harmful to humans but is that all?
魔香 對人類有害 但只有這樣嗎
I will report this to the principal.
這件事 我會跟學園長報告
They have a mission to carry out.
艾里他們正在執行任務
It's normal for them to not reveal everything.
有些事不能說也很正常
Let's just believe them.
就相信他們吧
Auguste, I envy your naivety.
奧古斯特 我真羨慕你的單純
I won't believe in anyone.
我可是誰都不相信
I'll go persuade him.
我去說服他
President James!
賽姆斯會長
Wait! I have something to say to you.
請留步 我有話跟你說
Is that so? Actually, I have a question for you.
是嗎 其實我也有話問你
Who are you?
你到底是誰
I've already said it just now...
剛才我已經說明過了…
Let me change my question.
我換個問題
You saw my true form, didn't you?
你…看到我的真面目了吧